[Taiki] It's Chinatsu and... Haryu?
[Taiki groans]
You know what,
I'm sure that they're just friends!
Like, look at us!
We're walking together, too!
Yeah, that makes sense!
Two people
walking together is normal, right?
Totally.
[Taiki] Yeah, totally... normal.
[inaudible]
What the...
- Both of them are seeded teams.
- Here's what I know.
It sounds like Haryu and Chinatsu
are in the same class,
and they sit next to each other.
What's more, they were
both elected class representatives.
- I don't know what those mean.
- 'Cause you're from different worlds.
SAME CLASS, SIT TOGETHER, BOTH REPS
But it's nothing to fret over.
Chinatsu said she wanted to focus
on basketball for now, remember?
Uh, yeah, that may be true.
But it's not like falling in love
is just a switch you can flip off!
I guess that's a good argument.
Almost sounds like
he pulled that from an anime.
[opening theme song playing]
BLUE BOX
EPISODE 3
CHII
What do you think about this year's batch?
Well, our core's going to be
the third-years, plus Kengo Haryu.
[assistant coach]
He's really that good, Coach?
[Coach Yuasa] He's got the potential
to dominate on the national level.
But I personally have high hopes
for where this first year is going.
[grunts]
[whistle blows]
[Chinatsu] Sorry! I'll get it.
[Taiki] Chinatsu.
Every time I see her now,
I keep flashing back to yesterday.
- Later.
- Ah, wait!
When are you done with practice today?
[Taiki gasps]
It's just I forgot my keys at home,
and, well, everyone said
they were going to be out late.
I should be done around 7:00.
Wait! What if someone
overhears our conversation?
Practice should be over by then.
- Okay, so then--
- Chii.
Does your team have an extra timer?
Ours is busted.
- [Taiki] "Chii"?
- [Chinatsu] I don't think we do.
- [Haryu] I figured.
- [Taiki] Did he just call Chinatsu "Chii"?
[Taiki running, panting]
I'm so jealous!
"Chii"! That means
they gotta be insanely close!
Why can't I use
a cutesy nickname for Chinatsu?
Plus, she didn't even think twice
about him calling her that.
- Hey, Chii!
- Hi!
[Taiki] What kind of vibe check
does a guy gotta pass with her?
- I wanna call you "Chii."
- Request approved.
[Taiki] Is it 'cause
they're in the same grade?
Or sit next to each other?
Or is it some sort of bond
that exists between the elite athletes?
[groans]
This is not a good look.
Trying to figure it out
won't change anything anyway.
It's not as if I can just
jump to the same grade as Chinatsu.
And even if she told me
I could call her Chii,
I don't think I'd able to.
If we weren't living together,
or in a situation
where using nicknames is normal,
I wouldn't even be thinking about it.
Chii... Chii... Chii...
- I'm home.
- Chinatsu!
[gasps] Something wrong?
No, everything is fine.
I'm such a creep! I'm such a creep!
What do you get if you
add pathetic and creepy? Me!
[Chinatsu sighs]
You got home fast huh, Taiki?
What?
As I was leaving practice,
the badminton team members
were only just getting to their clubroom.
You said you'd finish at 7:00,
but it seemed like
you guys were running late.
[Taiki] Yep, I've got it bad.
When she said,
"the badminton team members,"
I couldn't help but think
she really meant Haryu.
- Sorry, I'll be in my room--
- Oh, wait.
[grunts]
[groans]
My bad.
I just wanted to ask you something.
I'm going to be embarrassed if I'm wrong.
But did you run home?
It seemed like you were sweating,
so I thought you might've.
Did you... get home before me just so that...
I wouldn't be waiting outside for you?
- How'd she know what I was thinking?
- I did wait, but...
[Taiki] Here I was worrying about
something stupid like what I call her.
Knowing she was paying attention
to me makes me happy,
and it feels like
the other stuff doesn't matter.
[Chinatsu] If I am right...
it was a pretty good assist!
[Taiki exclaims]
That wasn't it at all!
I just thought I'd fit some more training
into my commute!
You know, I think I'll run a bit more now!
[Taiki] Having her move in with us
out of nowhere has me scrambled.
Haryu's not someone
I can take head-on anyway.
It doesn't matter who Chinatsu's with,
or what they call her...
I can't let myself worry
about every little thing.
Right now, I need to focus
on the club matches.
But I may still get triggered
when I hear him call her "Chii."
- [umpire] In! Game, Inomata!
- [Taiki pants]
[Kyo] You won another one.
Everything's going to plan.
[Taiki] Yeah! Then again,
I've mostly played first-years so far.
I haven't played
any of the regular members yet.
Also...
[Kyo] Haryu has won
every single one of his matches.
So, what's the update?
Did you decide what to do
about the two of them being so close?
[Taiki] Well, about that.
No matter what's going on between them,
I decided to not let it affect me.
If you're thinking about it that way,
it affected you.
For real! It feels so weird
being an upperclassman, right?
See, I don't care.
Okay, then why are you turning back?
[Chinatsu] Badminton's doing
a bracket within the club, right?
Yup, and this guy
hasn't lost a single match.
Yeah, so far I guess.
Don't be so modest.
This is where things get going.
I'm not done yet.
- Gotcha. Well, do your best!
- Thank you.
I don't care at all.
[Nishida] You two seem to be
getting along lately, huh?
You've been spending a lot of time
with Kano, haven't you?
I mean, our seats
are right next to each other.
- [groans]
- [Nishida] Mm-hm, is that all?
- [Kyo] He started melting.
- [Haryu] It's nothing.
We're both busy with our clubs.
[Haryu] But...
I do like girls who are
willing to go after what they want.
[Taiki] Wait. Does that mean...
[Haryu] It's not like that, bro!
[Taiki breathes heavily]
[Kyo] Wow, talk about
worst possible timing.
[umpire] Love all. Play!
[both grunting]
[umpire] In. Five to one!
Haryu's had the advantage this whole time.
He's not leaving any openings.
No kidding, he's like a brick wall.
Is he doing okay?
He's getting dominated.
That's just how it goes.
There's a difference
in their skill levels,
and a second-year's
gonna have more experience.
- [sighs] Oh, boy.
- [Kyo] This is rough on him.
His opponent gets along
with the girl he likes.
Then there's the possibility
that Haryu likes her, too.
And he's closer
to achieving Taiki's goals.
Exposing the differences between them,
it's like Haryu's telling Taiki to give up
on both nationals and Chinatsu.
Hm?
[shuttlecock thudding]
- [girl] Natsu!
- Coming!
[umpire] In. Eleven to four!
[boy 1] Haryu's gonna win
this one, too, huh?
[boy 2] He's a powerhouse.
Come on, somebody beat him!
You okay, dude?
Have some water.
Hey.
I was close to winning, right?
I wasn't in position in time.
The second I stop paying attention,
I get behind.
- You're doing well, though.
- Nah,
I've had a good run of it, that's all.
No, actually I thought...
other things would be bothering you.
Like what we overheard earlier.
Yeah.
Chinatsu's definitely one of the reasons
why I want to try harder and get better.
But to use her as an excuse when I lose...
that's not something I wanna do.
And it's not like I'm playing badminton
just for her sake.
The fact is that...
I love badminton.
- [boy] Taiki, ready to play?
- Okay!
[Taiki] It all may be true, but...
[gasps softly]
[gasps]
I made up my mind.
Even if it's one step, I'm taking it.
One step.
Oh, that was a good receive.
- [boy 1] Came right back though.
- [boy 2] Hang in there, Taiki!
[Taiki] One step.
[gasps]
[boy] It got lofted.
[Taiki grunts]
[Kyo] That was close. You were making
a comeback in the second half.
I think you should be proud of yourself.
You may have lost to Haryu today,
but considering your score,
I think you'll make the team.
[Taiki grunts]
You don't seem too happy.
Well, at the end of the day, I lost.
I scored in the second half,
but it felt like sheer willpower.
Haryu was setting the pace
for the entire match.
BURNABLE TRASH
[Taiki] I knew
that he was a strong player, but...
it's still annoying.
[pensive music playing]
Straight outta the horse's mouth.
The audacity of that little dweeb.
If anything, I'm the one who's annoyed.
Wait, why? You won though.
Because in the end...
[Nishida] Wait, now I've gotta know, man!
Come on! Tell me!
[Taiki] Well, I knew
it wasn't going to be easy.
After all, my opponent was Haryu.
You look at technique, speed, power...
He's got me beat in all areas of the game.
I need to play
on my own terms, have a plan.
Adjust my shots to my opponent,
and take the openings as they come.
In order to do that,
I need more experience.
I haven't practiced nearly enough.
Taiki.
- Come with me.
- Chinatsu?
Hurry the sun's going down!
Come on, let's go!
Uh, but... where are we going?
- A good spot.
- Hm?
[Taiki] Well, it certainly
is a good spot, but...
why are we in a park?
[Chinatsu] That would be because...
Ta-da!
Take a look at what I borrowed for us!
Hm? Why did you borrow rackets, Chinatsu?
[Chinatsu] You said
we should play sometime, right?
[Taiki gasps] She remembered I said that.
Besides, knowing you,
I thought there was a good chance
you would want to practice more.
You know, I usually wanna practice
the most right after a game.
And I thought you might be the same.
[Taiki] It makes me really happy
having someone in my life
who understands what I'm feeling.
[Chinatsu] Here it goes.
[happy music playing]
[laughs] She can't hit it?
Wait, it's not like that.
I just suck at serving.
[Taiki] Your left hand is moving too much.
Just drop the shuttle with it.
Then swing the racket forward.
Oh, you know what you're talking about!
It's just one of the basics.
[Chinatsu] Hold on, this is turning
into a practice session for me.
Shouldn't we work swings?
[Taiki] Don't worry about it. I got in
plenty of those during my matches!
I saw. Your match with Haryu today.
Erase that from your memory, please.
Why?
[Taiki] I mean, it was embarrassing.
I lost that match.
[Chinatsu] What's embarrassing about it?
You nailed that smash at the end, right?
[Taiki] Yeah, but still...
[Chinatsu] Don't forget...
at the interval of the second game,
it was eleven to four,
but by the time it got to 21 points,
Haryu had scored ten points,
and you had scored 11, Taiki.
Huh? Hmm, hmm. Hmm.
Losing is still losing, though!
I couldn't even score in the first half
because of my skill level.
And even if I scored in the second half,
it was still a loss.
[laughs]
[exclaims]
Wait. What's so funny about that?
Sorry, sorry.
You're not a big fan of losing,
are you, Taiki?
[Coach Yuasa] Don't swing
with your upper body. Use your legs.
[Taiki] Yes!
[Chinatsu] Whenever anyone calls out
an aspect of your play at practice,
you work on it the whole next morning.
And in your match against Haryu,
you never gave up, right?
You scored a lot in the second half.
That's why it's okay.
Taiki, you've got this!
[Taiki] Knowing how far I have to go,
it can be pretty challenging
to actually believe in myself.
I'll win the next one.
That's the spirit.
[Taiki] But having the support
of someone I like...
makes it so much easier.
YUKIKO
[Chinatsu] Oh. It's from Yukiko.
[Taiki] My mom?
She wants to know when we'll be back.
[Taiki] Chii?
Don't tell me Haryu...
gave that to her as a present?
Oh, this?
It was a gift from a friend in my class.
Yeah, almost everyone
in my year calls me Chii.
[gasps softly]
[Taiki] So, it turns out
Haryu wasn't special after all.
It seems Chinatsu
is friendly with everybody.
I guess she isn't
interested in dating right now.
Well, should we get going?
- You go on ahead.
- [exclaims]
I mean, there'll be
a lot of people on the way.
Maybe it isn't
such a big deal to you, Chinatsu,
but going to the same house with a girl...
would make me uncomfortable.
[Chinatsu exclaims]
I'm gonna be practicing my swings.
[grunts]
[Chinatsu] Not a big deal to me?
That's how it looks to him, huh?
EIMEI PRIVATE HIGH SCHOOL
[Taiki] Wait. Why?
DOUBLES
HARYU AND INOMATA
[Taiki] How'd I get partnered
with Haryu for doubles?
I'd been working out how to beat him,
and now we're playing together?
Yeah, you know what else?
Going to nationals with your love rival
is pretty weird.
Even if you forget the part
where I like Chinatsu, I...
- Taiki.
- [exclaims]
- Come on, let's get at it.
- Oh, sure thing.
For the time being, I'll start you
on the same training regimen as me.
[Taiki] Thank goodness.
It seems like
he didn't hear what I just said.
[Haryu] So...
I couldn't help but overhear
that you like Chinatsu?
[groans]
[whistle blows]
[Taiki] This is the worst start
to any doubles pair I've ever had!
You're too slow!
Fix your swing and feet!
Gotcha!
[boy 1] Man, Haryu's
like a drill sergeant.
This is all after they ran,
did circuit training, and footwork, right?
[boy 2] I'd be hurling by now
if it was me.
[panting]
I guess you're feeling worn out, then?
Say the word if you're done.
Would be a bummer if you passed out.
- Yes--
- Although, I can't say
that I've ever seen Chii mumbling
and grumbling during practice.
Chii's future boyfriend...
He must be a pretty cool guy
to go out with her.
[Taiki] All right, what are we doing next?
[Haryu] Five sets of two-minute rallies.
[school bell rings]
[groans softly]
He looks like a mushroom
that grew out of the desk.
And not a nutritious one either.
Stop talking.
I've been getting put through the ringer
over the last week.
The training has kicked my butt.
At this point, the classroom is
the only place I have left to chill out.
- Not home?
- [Kyo] Yeah, it took me by surprise.
I didn't expect him
to take you under his wing.
I thought that, even in a pair,
he'd be out for himself.
The guy that we're talking about...
is Haryu, the one we saw
walking together with Chinatsu?
Then this has gotta mean...
- he wants you to back off his crush.
- [exclaims]
Isn't that kinda the vibe?
- Our worlds are far apart.
- [Hina] Like he's trying to rub your nose
in your difference of status,
so you give up.
[Taiki groans] Well, it's working
'cause I am feeling it.
We do the same training,
but he never slows down.
And his shots are more accurate.
It must be so much more fun to play
when your foundation's that good.
- You nerd.
- Maniac.
[Taiki] Quit it with the insults!
[shuttlecock thudding]
[grunts]
Hey, Taiki. Why'd you do a cross there?
He was in backhand position.
And a straight shot
would've kept the shuttle's speed.
It would've been tougher for you,
but that was the right move.
You're never going to improve
if you only take the easy shot.
Got it!
I survived another day.
Back from battle?
[Taiki] Phew! I would kill for a drink.
[Kyo] Like a soft drink, right?
- Taiki.
- [exclaims]
- Nice hustle.
- [Taiki] Yeah, good practice.
Second-year upperclassmen and Chinatsu.
[chuckles]
So me and this guy got paired up
for doubles this year.
[gasps]
[Taiki] Why is he
talking about me right now?
This kid's a first-year,
and he's just utterly useless.
He has weaknesses everywhere you look.
His control sucks,
and he can get so flustered,
it ruins the play.
[Taiki] It's all true,
so I can't say anything.
But... I think he's gonna be a real force.
[grunts softly]
It doesn't really matter
how much I beat this guy up,
he's never once quit.
Even when I give him extra training
and it seems like
he'd never get through it,
he sticks with it until the very end.
[exclaims]
You are such a tyrant!
Ah, Haryu is hardest on the people
he expects the most from.
[Taiki gasps]
- [Haryu] No, that's not it.
- [Taiki] What a relief.
- He does have some faith in me.
- [boy] It is.
Anybody who's average, you ignore.
Right, Nishida?
- [Nishida] Huh?
- Sorry about him!
- [Chinatsu whispers] That's great to hear.
- You can be a nicer.
[boy] You know, the other day, there was
this first-year I was looking after...
[Taiki] Honestly,
getting noticed by an upperclassmen...
doesn't feel too bad.
Oh, look, I just got a text
from my girlfriend.
[chuckles] What? From your girlfriend?
[exclaims] Wait,
you have a girlfriend, Haryu?
- I do, since last week.
- [Taiki] Last week?
I've liked her for a long time,
but she works
in the entertainment industry.
I was about to give up on her,
but she ended up asking me out.
- [Taiki grunts]
- [Haryu] She's awesome.
She's had this dream since she was little,
and has really been going after it.
Chii, thanks for your help the other day.
It would've been tough
to buy makeup if I'd been by myself.
No problem.
[Taiki] Wait a second.
He knew all of this the whole time?
[amusing music playing]
Seems like getting a girlfriend for you
might be a ways off, champ.
[grunts angrily]
[Taiki] It's none of your business!
[closing theme song playing]